// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Could you tell me your Surname?",
    answer: "Would you like me to spell it?",
    options: [
      "Would you like me to spell it?",
      "Do you like my family name?",
      "How do I say that?",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "This plant looks dead.",
    answer: "It only needs some water.",
    options: [
      "It's in the garden.",
      "It only needs some water.",
      "It's sleeping.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "I hope it doesn't rain.",
    answer: "So do I.",
    options: [
      "Of course not.",
      "Will it be wet?",
      "So do I.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Are you going to come inside soon?",
    answer: "In a minute.",
    options: [
      "For ever.",
      "Not long.",
      "In a minute.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who gave you this book, Lucy?",
    answer: "I bought it.",
    options: [
      "I bought it.",
      "For my birthday.",
      "My uncle was.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Shall we go out for pizza tonight?",
    answer: "I'm too tired.",
    options: [
      "I know that.",
      "It's very good.",
      "I'm too tired.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Do you mind if I come too?",
    answer: "That's fine!",
    options: [
      "That's fine!",
      "I'd like to.",
      "I don't know if I can.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "There's someone at the door.",
    answer: "Well, go and answer it then.",
    options: [
      "Can I help you?",
      "Well, go and answer it then.",
      "He's busy at the moment.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How much butter do I need for this cake?",
    answer: "I'm not sure.",
    options: [
      "I'd like one.",
      "I'll use some.",
      "I'm not sure.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How long are you here for?",
    answer: "Till tomorrow.",
    options: [
      "Since last week.",
      "Ten days ago.",
      "Till tomorrow.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Have you guys had enough to eat?",
    answer: "Is there any more rice?",
    options: [
      "That's all right.",
      "Is there any more rice?",
      "It's not the right time.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "That's my coat over there.",
    answer: "Here you are.",
    options: [
      "Will you take it off?",
      "No, you haven't!",
      "Here you are.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Let's go by bus.",
    answer: "It'll take too long.",
    options: [
      "The train was expensive.",
      "We'll buy a ticket.",
      "It'll take too long.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Do you know my brother Charlie?",
    answer: "I don't think I do.",
    options: [
      "Sorry, he's not here.",
      "I don't think I do.",
      "I know.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Would you like some ice in your drink or not?",
    answer: "I don't mind.",
    options: [
      "I hope so.",
      "Yes, I shall.",
      "I don't mind.",
      "_ _ _"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "I hope I haven't ...... you any trouble by changing the arrangements.",
    answer: "caused",
    options: [
      "put",
      "caused",
      "made",
      "done"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "The floor is wet: don't run or you might ...... !",
    answer: "slip",
    options: [
      "stoop",
      "spill",
      "slip",
      "spin"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "When you come to my house, ...... your camera with you.",
    answer: "bring",
    options: [
      "take",
      "show",
      "fetch",
      "bring"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Paul arrived at the shop ....... as the manager was closing for the day.",
    answer: "just",
    options: [
      "even",
      "just",
      "still",
      "right"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "I would ...... to stay at home and relax for a change.",
    answer: "prefer",
    options: [
      "rather",
      "better",
      "prefer",
      "enjoy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Is there ...... of food for everyone?",
    answer: "plenty",
    options: [
      "adequate",
      "enough",
      "sufficient",
      "plenty"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Lily says she's happy at school but she's ...... complaining.",
    answer: "always",
    options: [
      "rarely",
      "sometimes",
      "always",
      "often"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 23,
    question: "...... the step when you go in.",
    answer: "Mind",
    options: [
      "Consider",
      "Mind",
      "Attend",
      "Look"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 24,
    question: "...... stay the night if it's too difficult to get home.",
    answer: "By all means",
    options: [
      "At all costs",
      "By all means",
      "In all",
      "On the whole"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 25,
    question: "No ...... Hannah is happy when you think how many prizes she has won recently.",
    answer: "wonder",
    options: [
      "surprise",
      "problem",
      "question",
      "wonder"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];